potbelly.com 2016-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Potbelly Sandwich Shop

## Privacy Notice 

(Updated November 4, 2016) 

Thank you for visiting Potbelly.com. Potbelly knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by our Websites, including our mobile websites and our mobile apps. By visiting Potbelly.com or using one of our mobile apps, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## The Information We Collect

We only collect personally identifiable information about you when you provide it voluntarily, by entering information on our Website, through our mobile apps or giving information to us in another way. For example, personal information may be collected when you order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion or subscribe to one of our services. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. The types of personally identifiable information that we may collect include: name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, birthday and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, such as aggregated data and anonymized data. For example, Potbelly may automatically collect website use information about the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system, domain name and information about your internet service provider.

## How We Use the Information

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not sell, transfer or disclose your personal information to any third parties other than for the limited purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services. With your permission, we may also use the information to communicate with you about our promotional offers, events or for other marketing purposes. 

We may also share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as providing technical services to our Websites) and that help us market our products. We share information with these companies only if they need it to perform their functions on our behalf and require them to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Potbelly may disclose personal information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request. In addition, we reserve the right to use and disclose your personal and non-personal information in order to (i) enforce our agreements, corporate policies and terms of use; or (ii) to protect the rights, property of Potbelly, our employees, agents, customers and others.

In the event of a merger, acquisition, financing or sale of assets or any other situation involving the transfer of some of all of our business assets, Potbelly may disclose your personal information to those involved in the negotiation or transfer.

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

## Cookies

To enhance your experience with our site we may use "cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We may use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize your favorite shop when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services.

Our Websites may also use web beacons or pixel tags, which are electronic images that may be used on our Websites or in our emails. We use these tools to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

## Children's Privacy Policy

Our site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. Potbelly does not knowingly request or collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

## Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online. While we take these reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information, no system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We may change our policy from time to time. Please check our policy frequently for changes.

## Gift Card Return Policy

Potbelly gift cards are non-refundable and cannot be redeemed for cash.

## Opt-Out

You have several options for updating or changing your personal information and how Potbelly communicates with you. Here are some of the ways you can request changes:

  * Follow the "unsubscribe" instructions at the bottom of email marketing communications to opt-out of receiving promotional emails.
  * Follow the “Update Your Information” instructions at the bottom of email marketing communications to manage your contact information (SMS text, email and postal address) preferences.
  * Text “STOP” to 43744 to opt-out from promotional SMS text messages.
  * Contact us at Talk To Us.

You can usually choose to set your browser to warn you when a cookie is being sent or to remove or reject cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie settings. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, it will affect many features or services on our Website.

## Potbelly Perks

With the Potbelly Perks app you’ll be able to order ahead, pay seamlessly, and earn amazing perks. Save time & skip the line by ordering via the app and we’ll have it ready when you arrive. Plus you can pay just by scanning your phone at the register—no wallet required! Best of all, the more you visit, the more rewards you’ll earn. Click here for the full terms and conditions of the Potbelly Perks program. 

## Questions and Feedback

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please Talk To Us or write us at:

Speaker of the House   
Potbelly Sandwich Shop   
111 N. Canal St. Suite 850  
Chicago, IL 60606 

  ©1977-2016 Potbelly Sandwich Works, LLC. All rights reserved.  
A First Class Dive, Potbelly, A Wreck, Ya Gotta Get It Hot, Potbelly Sandwich Shop and Potbelly restaurant interiors are trademarks owned and/or registered by Potbelly Sandwich Works, LLC.
